Kaio Fellipe

IT Manager

Security Analyst

CND in progress...

Contact me at

Linkedin: kaio-fellipe

Personal Profile

5 years of experience in systems and technology analysis, working in the areas of Management, Infrastructure, Security and IT Services. Experience in Business Intelligence, CRM, BPM, ERP implementation, ITIL, Office 365 and Infrastructure/Security standardization, following the best market practices. Experience in a national company in the Agribusiness segment. I am currently studying Information Security (Red and Blue Team), Python and NoSQL databases daily, for the development of personal and professional projects.

Skills summary	Level
Cyber Security	Advanced
Pentest	Intermediate
SQL	Expert
Python	Advanced
Project Management	Intermediate
Infrastructure Management	Advanced
IT Management	Advanced
Firewalls	Advanced
Computer Networks	Advanced
API REST	Intermediate
Linux servers	Intermediate
Windows servers	Intermediate
Virtualization	Intermediate

Skills summary	Level
SQL databases	Advanced
NoSQL databases	Intermediate
ETL process	Intermediate
Business Intelligence	Advanced

Languages

• Portuguese: Native

• English: Intermediate - Advanced

Work experience

Safra Rica (5+ years)

• IT Analyst (Jul. 2019 - Current)

As an IT Analyst, I was able to lead and participate in some project such as: standardizing the entire infrastructure of all our branches, implementation of the BPM methodology in the accounting and commercial areas, deployment of virtualized server infrastructure and the implementation of a data warehouse created by my team.

- Team leader (Manager)
- Database management
- SQL developer
- IT project leader
- BPM leader
- Network management
- Windows and Linux server management
- Local systems management
- Other administrative activities...
- IT Technician (Oct. 2017 Jun. 2019)

As an IT Technician, I was able to lead some projects such as: data center infrastructure readjustment, ERP migration, BI structuring, CRM software implementation, among others.

- Dashboard development for analysis using SQL
- Database administration
- Firewall administration
- Suport N2 and N3
- Network administration
- Local systems administration
- Windows servers administration
- Other administrative activities...

• Intern (Aug. 2016 - Sept. 2017)

As an intern, I was able to deploy the first firewall used in the company, building together a proxy and an IDS/IPS, a very large gain in quality and security of the connection was noticed.

- Computer maintenance
- Firewall configuration and maintenance
- Suport N1 and N2
- Network maintenance
- Requirements analysis for process improvements
- Administration of local systems
- Windows servers maintenance
- Other administrative activities...

Educational history

IGTI (2019 - 2020)

• MBA in IT Management

Senac (2018 - 2020)

Post graduate degree in Information Security

Unifafibe (2013 - 2017)

• Degree in Information Systems

Certificates

CND (in progress...)

Certified Network Defender by EC-Council

CSFPC (2021)

Cyber Security Foundation Professional Certificate by CertiProf

SFPC (2020)

• Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate by CertiProf

Network Security Analysis using Wireshark, Snort and SO (2019)

Udemy

Ethical Hacking Foundamentals (2017)

Udemy

Snort Intrusion Detection, Rule Writing, and PCAP Analysis (2017)

• Udemy

pfSense: Complete Firewall solution (2017)

Udemy